

Wai Lwin Aung

Full Stack Developer

Phone: 09796718690

Email: wailwinaung228@gmail.com

Address: ThaMarDi (2) Street, Ward 8, Mayangone

Township

Website: https://wailwinaung-dev.github.io/

OBJECTIVE

Greetings! I am Wai Lwin Aung, a skilled Full Stack Web Developer with a Bachelor of Computer Science degree. I have worked on various projects, including web and mobile applications, and have experience in using technologies such as **NodeJs**, **React Native**, **Typescript**, **MongoDB**, **CakePHP**, **Laravel**, **MySQL** and more. I am currently working as an Backend Developer at Young Investment Group Co., Ltd. Feel free to reach out to me at wailwinaung228@gmail.com or check out my portfolio at https://wailwinaung-dev.github.io/.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2017 Computer University (Monywa)

Bachelor of Computer Science(B.C.Sc)

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2023 - Now Young Investment Group Co., Ltd

Backend Developer

- Developing and maintaining an E-Wallet system.

July 2022 - January 2023 Brycen Myanmar Co., Ltd

Senior Engineer

- Bug fixing and implementing new features for an ERP

system.

- Providing technical guidance to junior developers.

- Collaborating with cross-functional teams.

May 2020 - July 2022 Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions

Full Stack Developer

- Developed and deployed projects.

- Maintained web applications.

- Implemented new features and bug fixes.

December 2019 - May 2020 Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions

Junior Web Developer

- Developed and maintained web applications.

- Implemented new features and bug fixes.

SKILLS

Language Burmese, English

Technologies React Native, Typescript, MongoDB, NodeJs, HTML5,

CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, React, Redux Toolkit, React Ionic, PHP, CakePHP, Laravel, Sail.js, Node-red, MySQL, Redis Queue, Firebase Cloud Messaging, Third-Party

Integration, Responsive Design, RESTful APIs, Git, Linux,

Docker

INTERESTS

I love riding bike, playing guitar.

REFERENCES

Name: Ko Aung Bo Htet

Position: DevOps Engineer

Name: Ma Yu Thandar

Position: Backend Developer

Company: Young Investment Group Co., Ltd Company: Young Investment Group Co., Ltd

Phone: 09950422293 Phone: 09880915229

PROJECTS

Unipay E-wallet System

(March 2023 - Now)

Customer	In-house project at Young Investment Group
Description	UniPay is a Local Acquirer Application for Merchants in Myanmar and is a Digital Payment Application that allows you to make cashless payments easily with just a phone as it is connected to multiple banking systems.
Team size	12 members
My position	Backend Developer
My responsibilities	- Bug fixing and implementation of new features to improve the Unipay system's functionality and performance - Collaboration with the development team to address system enhancements and maintenance tasks I contributed to the ongoing development and maintenance of the E-wallet system, ensuring the resolution of system issues and the successful implementation of new features.
Technologies used	NodeJs, React Native, ReactJs, AngularJs, Node-red, Elastic Search, WSO2 api manager, redis, firebase, AWS, MongoDB

Sumisho Global Logistics

(July 2022 - February 2023)

Customer	Sumisho Global Logistics
Description	The ERP System project involved the enhancement and maintenance of an existing ERP system for Sumisho Global Logistics.
Team size	10 members
My position	Senior Engineer at Brycen Myanmar Co., Ltd
	- Bug fixing and implementation of new features to improve the ERP

My responsibilities	system's functionality and performance - Collaboration with the development team to address system enhancements and maintenance tasks.
	I contributed to the ongoing development and maintenance of the ERP system, ensuring the resolution of system issues and the successful implementation of new features.
Technologies used	CakePHP 2, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, and MySQL

MMSpin Web App

(April 2022 - July 2022)

Customer	One of slipper whole sale company, I'm not sure
Description	The MMSpin Web App project involved the development of a web application for a promotion event purpose.
Team size	3 members
My position	Backend Developer at Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions
My responsibilities	 user can spin with voucher code to get promotion admin can manage vouchers, events, promotions and users. I was involved in creating the project from beginning to middle in backend process, including the development of a responsive web application for this system. And then I left from this company.
Technologies used	Laravel 9, REST API, React, Redux Toolkit, Metronic 8 Template, and MySQL

POS System

(August 2020 - January 2021)

Customer	Royal Studio Mandalay
Description	The POS System Web App was designed to facilitate sales and management processes for Royal Studio Mandalay's karaoke booking, managing session room, financial histories and services.
Team size	2 members
My position	Full Stack Developer at Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions
My responsibilities	 Allow to track room, check in, check out, reserved, calling waiter Provide to manage booking Generates reports on financial histories. I was involved in creating the project from beginning to end for the POS system.
Technologies used	CakePHP 4, REST Api, React, Redux Toolkit, Material UI, and MySQL

Mickhae Karaoke iOS App

(March 2020 - July 2020)

Customer	Voice Industry and Royal Studio Mandalay
Description	The Mickhae Karaoke iOS App was developed to cater to the voice industry and Royal Studio Mandalay, providing a platform for karaoke enthusiasts.
Team size	2 members
My position	Full Stack Developer at Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions

My responsibilities	 Integration of karaoke features, filtering songs, choosing songs, calling waiter and so on. Seamless audio and video playback functionalities Challenges: Overcoming compatibility issues across various iOS IPad devices and optimizing the app's performance for smooth audio and video playback.
	I led the development of the iOS app, ensuring a seamless and engaging karaoke experience for users.
Technologies used	CakePHP 4, REST Api, Ionic React(Typescript), Redux, and MySQL

ZDS Myanmar Delivery Management System (July 2019 - December 2019)

Customer	Myanmar Zarla Distribution Co., Ltd
Description	ZDS Myanmar Delivery Management System is a web application developed for Myanmar Zala Distribution Company to streamline their delivery operations.
Team size	3 members
My position	Junior Web Developer at Sabahna Corporate Digital Solutions
My responsibilities	- Responsive and user-friendly web application - Allows delivery personnel to track and manage deliveries - Provides updates to customers on the status of their deliveries - Generates reports on delivery performance and efficiency - Generates reports on financial process I was involved in creating the project from beginning to end, including the development of a responsive web application for the delivery system.
Technologies used	CakePHP 3, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, MySQL, Limitless Responsive web application Template